Our Privacy Policy

We are very delighted that you have shown interest in our service. Data protection is of a particularly high priority for the management of Career Soft, LLC. This privacy policy will explain how and when our organization collects and uses personal data from you when you use our websites or mobile apps.

Topics:

* What data do we collect?
* How do we collect your data?
* How will we use your data?
* How do we store your data?
* Marketing
* What are your data protection rights?
* What are cookies?
* How do we use cookies?
* How to manage your cookies
* Privacy policies of other websites
* Changes to our privacy policy
* How to contact us
* How to contact the appropriate authorities

What data do we collect?
========================

Career Soft LLC collects various types of data depending on how you use our websites and mobile applications.

Our websites and mobile apps can be used without creating an account to view information about events. Some data we collect without you explicitly providing it:

* Anonymous analytics information about how you use our websites and applications which may include unique device identifiers.

If you create an account on our website or mobile apps, you may or may not provide us with  the following information:

* Personal information, including:

* Name
* Email address
* Phone number
* Profile picture
* Etc.

* In addition, for candidates, you may or may not provide us with your educational and work background, including:

* Resume
* GPA
* Major or discipline
* School year
* The types of work positions you are seeking
* Your work authorization or visa status
* Etc.

* For recruiters, you may or may not provide us with:

* Who you are employed by
* Any candidates you may have spoken with
* Ratings or notes that you recorded for any candidate

How do we collect your data?
============================

You directly provide Career Soft LLC with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:

* Create a student account through our website or mobile applications
* Are invited and accept an invitation as a recruiter in our system
* Sign up for appointments with recruiters through our system
* Rate or make notes on candidates through our system

Career Soft LLC may also receive your data indirectly from the following sources:

* Your college, university, or other event-hosting organization may provide us with your email address in order to invite you to the system

How will we use your data?
==========================

Career Soft LLC collects your data so that we can:

* Connect students and candidates with recruiters representing organizations they may be interested in
* Provide recruiters with a way to view, manage, and contact students and candidates they are interested in hiring
* Allow event organizers, including college and university career center staff, to view your data in order to:

* Provide assistance to recruiters and candidates
* Reach out to provide information about the event, promote the event, and for other event-related communications

* Provide customer support
* If you have signed up to receive such communications, Career Soft LLC may send emails to users alerting them of updates to our blog or potential new products or services

How do we store your data?
==========================

Career Soft LLC utilizes various Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) and Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) providers to securely store your data. Data is physically stored in the Amazon Web Services or Google Cloud Services Data Centers in the United States of America in the following regions: AWS's us-east-1 and us-east-2 regions and Google's us-east1 and us-east4 regions. All data is automatically backed up nightly and, if corrupted, can be easily restored via tools provided by the third-party PaaS/SaaS providers.

For more information about the third-party services we use to store your data, see the following links:

Google, Inc.

Amazon Web Services, Inc.

Intercom, Inc.

MongoDB, Inc.

Stripe, Inc.

Career Soft LLC will maintain your data as long as you choose. At any time you make revoke permission for us to maintain your data by deleting your profile through the website or mobile applications. Deleting your profile removes all personally identifiable information (PII) from our system.

Marketing
=========

If you are a user of the Career Soft LLC my.careerfairplus.com webpage we would like to send you information about products and services of ours that we think you might like.

If you have signed up to receive updates about our blog, newsletter, or other services, Career Soft LLC will occasionally contact you for those purposes.

If you have agreed to receive marketing, you may always opt-out at a later date.

You have the right at any time to stop Career Soft LLC from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your data to any partner companies.

If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please [click here to unsubscribe](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://goo.gl/forms/iimYLgkjEe7686Fw2&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1620334887489000&usg=AOvVaw0k3Vn5D60xxuTDJGJI-Asn).

What are your data protection rights?
=====================================

Career Soft LLC would like to make sure you are fully aware of all your data protection rights.

Every user is entitled to the following:

The right to access - You have the right to request copies of your personal data held by Career Soft LLC. We may charge you a small fee for this service.

The right to rectification - You have the right to request that Career Soft LLC correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request Career Soft LLC to complete any information you believe is incomplete.

The right to erasure - You have the right to request that Career Soft LLC erase your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to restrict processing - You have the right to request that Career Soft LLC restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to object to processing - You have the right to object to Career Soft LLC’s processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to data portability - You have the right to request that Career Soft LLC transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us:

Email us: [support@careerfairplus.com](mailto:support@careerfairplus.com)

Or write to us at:

Career Soft, LLC

10524 Moss Park Rd. Ste 204

#123

Orlando, Florida 32832

United States

What are cookies?
=================

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technology.

For further information, visit [https://www.allaboutcookies.org/](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.allaboutcookies.org/&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1620334887493000&usg=AOvVaw2VGTN8pWJOhi9VErypYrYy).

How do we use cookies?
======================

Our company uses cookies in a range of ways to improve the experience on our website, including:

* Keeping you signed in
* Understanding how you use our website
* Saving information you enter into our website so that it is not lost between sessions
* To better assist you when you have questions/chats with our customer support staff

How to manage your cookies
==========================

You can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website (see What are cookies?) tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.

Privacy policies of other websites
==================================

Career Soft LLC websites and mobile apps contain links to websites and services outside of the control of Career Soft LLC. Our privacy policy applies only to our websites and mobile apps and you should read the privacy policies of any linked website, mobile app, or other services before using those sites.

Changes to our privacy policy
=============================

Career Soft LLC keeps its privacy policy under regular review and makes any updates publicly available via our websites and mobile apps. This privacy policy was last updated on 23 July 2020.

How to contact us
=================

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.

Email us: [support@careerfairplus.com](mailto:support@careerfairplus.com)

Or write to us at:

Career Soft, LLC

10524 Moss Park Rd. Ste 204

#123

Orlando, Florida 32832

United States

How to contact the appropriate authorities
==========================================

Should you wish to report a complaint or if you feel that Career Soft LLC has not addressed your concern in a satisfactory manner, and you are a resident of the EU, you may contact the International Commissioner’s Office by visiting [https://ico.org.uk/](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://ico.org.uk/&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1620334887497000&usg=AOvVaw3A3Y6ATUx-nbzD0Xw8aPZ-).
